A Guide to the Barry C. Smith papers FA794
Rockefeller Archive Center
Barry C. Smith papers
1916-1961
Rockefeller Archive Center
Smith, Barry C.
Commonwealth Fund
FA794
1.73 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box, 1 half-legal document box and 1 flat file folder
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research, with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Arranged as received.
Scope and Contents
The Barry C. Smith papers include Commonwealth Fund Annual Reports (1919-1941), personal and professional correspondence and a variety of personal items.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Barry C. Smith papers were donated to RAC in 2015 and accessioned as 2015:107.
Biographical / Historical
Smith served as General Director of the Commonwealth Fund from 1920 to 1947.
- The Commonwealth Fund, Annual Reports, 1919-1925 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Commonwealth Fund, Annual Reports, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Commonwealth Fund, Annual Reports, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Commonwealth Fund, Annual Reports, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Commonwealth Fund, Annual Reports, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Edward R. Morrow Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Robert A. Lovett Correspondence, 1951 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Photographs - Barry C. Smith portrait (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Untitled-Unidentified photos, 2015:107:001 (Box SF1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Separated items are restricted from access until they have been stabilized.
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (still images) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
- Yale Graduation Address, 1946 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Information Bureau, Report, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Proceeding of Mayors Conventio (Mayors Association of the South Atlantic and Gulf States), held in Jacksonville, Florida, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Untitled photos, 2015:107:002 (Box SF1)
- Passports - Barry C. Smith and T. R. Smith (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Mr. and Mrs. Barry Smith Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1921-1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Journal of the Tennesee, State Medical Association, 1936 January (Box 1, Folder 15)
- First Meeting of the Tufts College Medical School Council - Address, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Commonwealth Fund Newsletter (In Memorium: Edward Stephen Harkness), 1940 February (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Litton Industries (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Untitled photos, 2015:107:003 (Box SF1)
- National Order of the Legion of Honour - Chevalier - France - Awarded to Barry Smith, 1920 (Folder 1, Folder 19)
  Flat file - Restricted from access until it has been stabilized.